Pedro Bracher Duarte

Full Stack Developer

I am a Software Developer with a Bachelor's degree in Civil Engineering and 5 years of experience as an entrepreneur. My key attributes include strategic and logical vision, high capacity for fast learning and problem-solving, alongside strong relational and communicative abilities, which have allowed me to lead two companies in different industries. Since 2022, I am looking to apply these skills to a new developer role.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer, Kuke

02.2023 - present

As Kuke's sole Full Stack Developer, I led a significant transition to a subscription-based model using Python, Django and AWS. Key achievements include:

- Developing an integrated platform for client registration and order placement, which automated operations and boosted efficiency.
- Managing a growing client base of over 100 and facilitating more than 400 orders monthly.
- Integrating Snipcart for order management, Stripe for payments, and Zapi for WhatsApp notifications through the use of RESTful APIs and Webhooks.
- Crafting a user-friendly dashboard for enhanced client, order, and subscription management.

Full Stack Developer, Novamente Software House

10.2022 - 01.2023

- Worked closely with clients to gather requirements, validate development stages, and ensuring product aligns with client expectations.
- Led the design and development of robust databases using PostgreSQL, ensuring data integrity and optimal performance.
- Utilized Ruby on Rails for back-end development and leveraged HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, and Javascript for responsive front-end designs.
- Conducted regular code reviews and utilized Git and Github for efficient version control.
- Hosted and maintained applications on Heroku, ensuring optimal uptime and performance.
- Promoted agile methodologies, collaborating with the development team in sprint formats

Co-Founder, Ambra Real Estate Development Ltda

07.2018 - 07.2022

- Construction industry firm;
- Constructed and marketed 10 houses 1020 m²;
- Role as Civil Engineer and Developer.

Co-Founder, *Peracanga Foodpark*

11.2017 - 02.2022

- Entertainment and Gastronomy industry firm;
- Conducted 4 events 60 commercial partners 120,000 customers;
- Role as Executive, Commercial, and Financial Manager.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon, Web Development - Bootcamp 07.2022 – 09.2022

Fundação Getúlio Vargas, MBA Real Estate Construction and Incorporation Management 07.2017 – 12.2018

Federal University of Espírito Santo (UFES), Bachelor in Civil Engineering 08.2011 – 12.2016

SKILLS

Python | Django | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | JavaScript | Html | CSS | Bootstrap | Postgresql | Figma | Git Github | Heroku | Scrum | React | AWS

A LANGUAGES

Portugues • • • • English • • • • • Spanish • • • • • German